They are in projection
you asked for. General.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
You clear. go ahead.
There's been a complication
Burrows and Scofield
had been transferred to...
I read the newspapers.
you don't have to tell
me what's in the headlines.
The exact penitentiary where they
are been held is under disclosed.
But you can guarantee
the Federal...
- Supermax.
- No more updates.
Call me when they are dead.
Welcome to Los Angeles.
As it turns out.
men who have escaped not one. but two penitentaries
are considered as a bit of fight risks.
So we need to know where you are
and what you're doing at all times.
These are GPS ankle monitors.
Now step up. take one and put it on.
I ain't wearing that.
Let's make this clear
I'm your ally.
but more importantly. I'm your boss.
Which means if this fails...
it's my ass on the line
as much. if not more.
than yours. so from this point on.
if I ask you to do
something. you do it.
If I ask you to say something.
you say it.
And if I ask you to put on a monitor...
you put on a monitor.
As far as the general
public is concerned.
you're being contained in a
Supermax facility somewhere
in the United States.
So to avoid any messy explanations
and stay off the Company's radar.
you need to keep
your heads down and your ears open.
We've provided cell phones.
clothing. and toiletries
all the basic necessities
to get you up and running.
Hey. uh. you-you patted
these guys down
before you let them in. right?
'Cause I can't be getting
shanked or shivved.
Who's this?
This is Roland Glenn.
He'll be assisting you.
We've already got our team.
No. Scofield. see. this is my team.
And Roland's working off
a sentence just like the rest of you.
In fact. with the amount of security
that's gonna be around Scylla.
Roland's expertise will be a necessity.
So. if no more questions.
let's get to work on finding Scylla.
What about that second step?
What about the break-in?
You let me worry about step two. okay?
You just worry about finding Scylla.
I've got an idea where to start.
That's excellent. Alexander.
See. there's a man who's thinking.
All right. let's let these men
get to work.
Good luck!
To all of us.
Yeah. since I was
here first. I think I'll
just go ahead and grab that
S.S. bedroom. if that's cool.
- Sara?
- Yeah?
You take the bunk.
You know. when this is.
when this is all done...
you and me.
we're gonna settle up.
All right. obviously.
there's a lot of history in this room.
That's a given.
But it we're gonna pull this off.
it's gonna take all of us.
We got to work together.
So if anyone has a
problem. get it out now.
You want to clear the
air with someone...
now's the time.
All right.
Let's get to work.
Whistler's assignment was to drop off
this. this. this data card...
this--this 'Scylla' to
a Company Executive.
Someone he referred
to as "The Cardholder."
And his job was to--to protect it.
To... keep it safe.
Now. I didn't...
see who he was. but I
got a look at his driver.
His driver?
You want to sketch this guy's face
and match it up to 10
million people in Los Angeles?
Well. that's just great.
I saw more than just the guy's face.
All the drivers were
hanging around. talking shop.
but this guy. he was
standing by himself.
Legs apart. hands behind his back.
at rest he's former military.
His car...
rides a little lower
than the rest of 'em.
Probably signifies private security.
Weighed down by bulletproof siding.
His suit. his suit...
you don't buy a suit like that
on a cop's salary or pulling
weekend gigs as a driver.
That means he's full-time.
He's highly paid.
You ask our friend
Mr. Self to run tax records
on 45 to 55-year old white males
in Los Angeles drawing
a military pension.
and taking six figures from
a private security company.
and you narrow your field
from 10 million till about 50.
And then I can pick
the guy out from there.
Find the driver. you
find the Card Holder.
We haven't ate or
drank anything for days.
Oh. I don't want
to die out here.
We ain't gonna die. Sancho.
Hey. hey. we ain't gonna die.
- Okay.
- We just gotta find...
what's called a compass cactus.
Due to the fact it always
leans toward the south.
Inside there's delicious fruit
which'll fill our bellies.
Plus. we find out which way is south.
we're gonna find out
which way is north.
Comprende?
Tell you what.
Why don't we. uh. rest
here for a while. huh?
Travel at night when it's cooler.
Si. That sounds good.
What are we gonna do
when we get there?
To San Diego.
You mean after Michael pays
for the vile he's transgressed upon me?
I'm still trying to
figure that out.
Nice to work with Homeland.
The FBI would take days
to gather this Intel.
Well. the FBI should'a hired me
'cause I could've gotten
whatever info you wanted
in 25 minutes tops.
You some kind of hacker?
I design silicon lithography
for personal gain.
He's an identity thief.
He's a douche.
Hey. why don't you sit in the corner
and we'll get you
when we need you.
This is him.
That's the driver.
Now what?
Well. he takes us
to the Cardholder.
and the Cardholder
takes us to Scylla.
You could have left
me there. in jail.
Could have or should have?
Maybe both.
Are you thanking me. Alex?
- I don't know.
- Don't bother.
You're here because we needed you.
- Not because we wanted you.
- That's him.
That's the guy.
What's that. private security?
This thing's a fortress.
Alright. slow down.
Slow down.
This thing we gotta get.
it's in there?
We have motion sensors.
alarm systems.
armed guards.
In and out of that place
without anybody knowing.
You better have one
hell of a plan. Michael.
So. basically. there's no
freaking way to break-in...
- ...to the place.
- Not quickly.
Not without being seen.
What about the neighbors.
uh. somewhere we can be staged
from. you know.
go under and up?
Closest neighbor is
here. across the street.
And even that would take weeks.
The government's story
about us being held in a Supermax
will only last so long.
What does that mean?
I mean.
then what if somebody
finds out we're not.
What if we don't have
to be in the house?
If the card. this Scylla.
is so important...
maybe the guy is carrying it on him.
Well. according to
public records. the owner
of the estate's name is Stuart Tuxhorn.
and he's a CEO of a
company called Spectroleum.
Heavy hitter like that's
gonna have security 24-7.
And we gotta get this thing
without anyone
knowing it's gone. right?
So even if he's got it on
him. how do we get it off him?
You don't steal the card.
You copy it.
Oh. now you're interested
in what I gotta say. right?
Copying it will make it harder.
Not only do you have to steal it.
you have to return it. genius.
Only if you don't got me. "hombre".
What's that?
This is the reason I got busted.
Oh. you stole the cell phone?
Oh. yeah. yeah. no.
I'm lookin' at federal time 'cause
I stole a cell phone. seriously.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa!
I invented this so that
I don't have to steal.
It looks like a cell phone but it's
really like a digital black hole.
Wireless hard drive that
swallows up any electronic data
within ten feet of it.
Like what?
Like the account info
of anyone at Starbucks
with a latte and a laptop.
Like the PIN number of any
credit card used at a gas pump.
I can walk out of here
and get the identities
and financial statements of
ten people in ten minutes.
on a slow day.
with one hand on my junk.
And the information embedded in Scylla?
If we can get close enough...
It's ours.
"Breaking and Entering"
Edits: VeRdiKT [subscene.com]
Is this number...
acceptable to you?
10.000 people?
- Yes.
- Good!
Now that you're on board.
we can issue the op-order today.
He's on his way.
All right. hold on.
Sara. it's me.
Everybody's on.
Okay.
Now. while I'm monitoring the device.
I'm not gonna be able to see
exactly what data's being copied.
But. like downloading
quality porn from the Internet.
progress bar's gonna tell me
when it's time to rock and roll.
How long do they
need to stay in range?
Encrypted data like this is
gonna take at least two minutes.
Here he comes.
Sucre. you're on.
Good luck!
Easy.
Sir. would you mind stepping
away from the vehicle?
Talk to me. Roland.
I got nothing. man.
Last time I had this
little action. I was
dry humping my way
through the fifth grade.
Calm down!
Sir...
Step away from the vehicle!
It's okay. bro. just relax.
we don't have to get all excited.
So you speak English now.
Only a little. but. uh...
How about now?
Nada.
Try to get closer to them.
If he was any closer.
he'd be in the car.
I get your little act. Pedro.
Hit the brakes.
let the rich guy pay for
damage you don't intend to fix.
Just give the man some money
so we can leave.
Congratulations!
- He was there.
- I think Tuxhorn was in the car.
- So did we get it or not?
- Nope.
Nothing.
Can I help you?
So how did you find me?
I never lost you.
The. uh. the new nose
threw me a bit. but--
What do you want. Don?
I got customers.
Look. back in the days. when
you worked with the Company...
Well. for the Company.
I did economic forecasts
of their operations.
I mean. I wasn't one of the guys--
But you had access.
Come on.
the last time I helped you.
the only thing I got out of it
was plastic surgery
and a $100.000 pay cut.
You know. so either you buy
one of these exceptional family cars.
with above average gas mileage.
or you leave me the hell alone.
I know about Scylla.
And I'm going after it.
You know. I knew you were crazy.
I didn't know you were stupid. too.
Well. let's just say I was
able to get hands on it.
It's my understanding that
Scylla could only be used
if it's plugged into a decoder box
that's hidden in one of the
Company facilities. Am I right?
You know. I wish I could help.
but I can't.
No. you are helping. Jasper.
Just a matter of whether
you do it before or after
I shame you in front
of your co-workers here.
Tell me where the Company
keeps the box. Jasper.
Could be anywhere.
I don't know.
Somebody does.
Right?
Somebody that you might
have access to.
You know. if you go down this road.
your government job
won't protect you.
Then I better not
get caught. right?
If I don't find something to eat soon.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm not gonna make it.
We just got to keep...
got to keep talking. Sancho.
Keep our brains focused
on something other than
our empty bellies and
our dry mouths. okay?
Come on!
Let's start with. uh.
your-your favorite color.
Aah. hell you doing?!
I'm hungry. Teddy.
Why should the both of us die
out here when one of us
could help the other one survive?
You don't want to do this. Please!
I'll make it quick. I promise!
Sancho?
Sancho!
Why'd you have to go
and do something so...
so Tuxhorn doesn't have
the card on him.
It gotta be in there. right?
Look. there's no way we're getting
on that house without being seen.
I know.
Well. if the card's in
there. how are we gonna copy it?
We're not.
She's gonna do it for us.
What you reading?
"There is no fighting her.
"No power can fight her.
"All that avails is flight."
That's Homer.
That's from The Odyssey.
- Is this from my father's folder?
- Yeah.
And it explains why
Scylla sounded so familiar.
If I'm not mistaken. it's
from that chapter in the book
where Odysseus is told
he has to confront a monster...
...known as Scylla.
Wonder why he wrote this down.
I could be wrong.
but I believe
Odysseus is told that in order to
continue on his path.
to pass Scylla.
it'll require the
sacrifice of six of his men.
His only other alternative
is to abandon his path
and he chooses to
make the sacrifice.
Well. it's a hell of a choice.
One I'm not sure I'm
comfortable making.
Sara. um. about tomorrow.
the plan.
housekeeper...
If you're not up to it--
No. no. I am.
Tell me. is Claudia
Mauricio a good roommate?
A good person?
I hope she feels the same about you.
Oh. Shelby. you wouldn't believe
the traffic on the...
You'll want to be quiet now.
Claudia.
There are levels of clearance
at the Department of Corrections
that are simply not available.
even for friends as connected as mine.
So. listen carefully.
If you even remotely
value your friend's life.
You're going to use your
security code to access
the records for prisoner transfers.
And tell me where they
sent Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows.
Can I take that for you?
Thanks! Sure.
That's a great bag.
Can I ask you where you got it?
It was a gift from my boss.
so I don't really know.
Sorry.
- Sure.
- Thanks!
There you go.
I. uh... I can never find a good bag.
I'm a teacher.
and I have books
and grading materials and...
I should probably go ahead and just
invest in a wagon one of these days.
Yeah. that's why I love this bag.
It has so many pockets.
Do you mind if I take a look?
Oh. no.
Thanks.
Oh. thank God. thank God!
You all right. mister?
Yeah. my damn truck blew
a gasket a few miles back.
I've been. uh. hoofing it ever since.
Where you headed?
San Diego.
Hell. we can give you
a ride. if you'd like.
Hey. what's wrong. man?
Eat some bad Mexican?
Something like that.
Same as yesterday.
right on schedule.
She better have that
thing in her purse.
Tuxhorn Residence.
Hello. I'm from the alarm company.
We've been receiving some. uh.
strange signals from your property.
We'd like you to check
the windows. please.
Make sure all the
contacts are still active.
All the windows?
Yes. ma'am.
Every room in the house.
Okay. hold on.
Does she still have the bag?
Yeah.
She's got it.
I'm picking up all kinds
of gak from the house. man.
Small stuff. maybe a digital
camera. an MP3 player.
Nothing of the size of what
we're looking for. though.
Keep her moving.
So far. so good. ma'am.
Uh. please move on
to the next room.
How we doing?
Still don't got it.
If the card's in there.
it'd be in some kind of a... safe. office.
Ma'am. our system is showing
that the malfunction
is coming from a room
that's designated as.
uh. an office or a den.
You mean the library?
Mister doesn't like me going in there.
Well. I think he'd like it
even less if you went home
without properly setting the
alarm first. don't you think?
All right. I'll check.
We got something.
The card?
Oh. yeah!
File's so big it can't be anything else.
Now you just gotta keep her there
for two minutes while
it finishes the burn.
Stall her. we need two minutes.
Ma'am. I think we found
the source of our problem.
If you could just stay
at that particular window
and hold it closed while we reset
the system. that should do it.
Talk to me. Roland.
It's almost there.
almost. almost.
Come on. come on.
come on. come on.
Come on.
- Got it!
- Got it.
All right. ma'am. thank
you so much for your help.
All we need to do
now. man. is just...
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
she's heading back inside.
- What for?
- I don't know.
Oh. no.
No. we're good.
She's out.
Hey! Oh!
Hey. stop it!
Just wait here.
I actually had to slow down
not to catch you.
I think I pulled a groin.
It's not in the bag.
- It's not here.
- How could it not be in here?
The device. it's not here.
Give me it!
Son of a bitch!
Twenty-six. twenty-seven.
twenty-eight...
Go ahead.
Before Burrows and Scofield
were allegedlly transferred
to Arlington. someone posted their bail.
I need to know who.
I'm showing a Bruce Bennett.
former aid to Governor
Frank Tancredi.
You think it fell out?
We looked everywhere.
You think we got the thing copied?
Like I said. I can't read the content
without downloading the device. but...
unless this Tuxhorn's got.
like. a 50.000-hour TiVo.
then. yeah. I think we got it.
Doesn't matter if we got it
if we can't find it.
Where the hell is it?
It's still inside the house.
That's why the maid went back inside.
She must have found it.
assumed it belonged to her boss.
and then she left it behind.
Well. then guess what.
fellas. it's game over.
You know how many months it took
me to make that thing. Michael?
What. you just think I
can whip up another one
- in a couple of seconds?
- Losing it is not the problem.
If they find it. that's the problem.
If they find out someone was
after that card. we're done.
What do you mean. done?
What does that mean?
Does that mean we're
gonna go back to prison?
Are they gonna kill us?
- What the hell does that mean?
- Shut up!
Means we're going in to get it.
If we had a few days.
we could figure out
a way to pull this off. but I gather
we don't have that kind of time.
Yeah. you gather right.
Look. if you want us to get that device
out of there. you gotta throw us a bone.
give us some extra help.
What you're asking for requires
involving additional people.
which. given the covert
nature of this operation.
I cannot do.
Then you're asking for the impossible.
No. what I'm asking
for is competence. okay?
I'm not the one who
put the entire mission
in the hands of a damn maid.
Look. if the Company finds that
copy of Scylla before we do.
that's it. Michael. that's ball game.
They're gonna find
out who was behind it.
and they're going to ghost us.
All of us.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Look. I didn't choose you to do this
because I had you in custody.
I chose you to do this because
I believed you could pull it off.
Yeah. well. a lot of people have believed
in me in the last few months. Agent Self.
Not all of them are alive today.
Can you get me back the device or not?
All right. this is what we got.
The housekeeper saw the device
as she was leaving the house.
Then she disappears back
inside for 15 seconds.
So. we know. wherever it is.
it's somewhere close to the door.
So. 15 seconds.
that's all we gotta buy ourselves.
Listen. I'm not sure how close we're gonna
get to this house. let alone inside of it.
but let's-let's say that we do.
The alarm they got installed
in this house is triggered
1.2 seconds after broken
contact in any door or window.
Which would immediately send
the private security guards
with their 47 guns
rushing into the property.
And after 30 seconds. the alarm company
will dispatch vehicles to the property.
Three to four. depending
on availability.
After confirmation of a break-in.
they'll dispatch additional vehicles
to seal off any and all
exits from the property.
I don't know about this. Michael.
It's getting pretty clear why they
hired a bunch of cons to do this job.
It's not because they
wanted it off the books.
It's because we're expendable.
Who's gonna care if a bunch
of crooks wind up dead?
It's suicide.
I'm gonna keep looking
and see what I can find.
That quote from The Odyssey.
What about it?
I just. I can't shake that line.
"All that avails is flight."
What if flight is our only option. Linc?
What if our father after
everything he discovered
about the Company.
what...
...what if that's what
he finally realized?
You know. uh. the one
thing I remember most
about Dad was the
back of his head.
Always walk out the front door.
Always running from something.
Mom. us. himself.
But the one thing he
never ran away from
was his belief that the
Company needed to be taken down.
And we got an opportunity to do that.
Then this is our fight. not theirs.
Man. this... this ain't Fox River.
These guys chose to be here.
Remember that.
They got a choice.
Almost...
Ready?
Go!
- Let's go! Let's go! Go!
- The side-doors are locked...
Go!
- Come on.
- Let's go!
Where's it coming from?
It's across the street.
Come on.
Go.
Just something across the street.
We got a team checking it out now.
You can get back inside. sir.
That must be out of town.
Yes!
Daddy. is everything okay?
Alex...
Thanks. Jim!
Alex!
Let's go!
Go!
Don't turn around...
unless you'd like to
experience a great deal of pain
over an even greater length of time.
You-you know. just-just
take whatever you want here.
The only thing I want from you.
Bruce. is the answer
to a simple question:
Where are Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows?
I only know what-what I
read in the papers and--
Three days ago. there were a
105 inmates in the Supermax wing
of the U.S. penitentiary
in Livingston. Texas.
where the brothers were allegedly sent.
There are still 105 inmates there and no
one has been released during that time.
Someone is playing a shell game. Bruce.
I'm just trying to find out who.
I have no criminal jurisdiction over...
I know you bailed them out.
I know you've been in
contact with Sara Tancredi.
I swear to you. I-I have
no idea where they are.
I guess we'll see about that.
Good luck. Teddy!
Who needs luck when you got
friends like you fellas. huh?
Hey. you mind if I take this
old newspaper of yours with me?
No problem.
Sorry to hear about your friend. dude.
Ahh. it's all right.
He had a full life.
Later. Teddy.
There you go.
Thirty-six.
twenty-four.
thirty-six.
Did you get it?
Let's make sure we got
what we wanted.
- Linc.
- Yeah.
Don't let that thing out of your sight.
All right.
We're halfway there.
All we got to do is
that little B and E. and...
we're out of here.
Reminds me. I need to get ahold of Self.
see when we can get started.
So what are you gonna do
when all this is over?
That's a good question.
Brother. whatever this Scylla thing is.
it is a monster of a code.
Sara. I was gonna come down here
and ask if you wanted to talk some more
about what happened in Panama.
but. um. I think I already
know what you're gonna say.
How's that?
Because you're a little like me.
Because you're gonna say you're
fine. that you can handle it.
So. umm...
I'll just leave it at this.
I'm here.
Whenever you want to talk...
Thank you!
You know that the only
thing that kept me alive
when I was being held was
the thought of being with you.
But I also knew that if
anything happened to me.
you were gonna blame yourself. and
you would spend the rest of your life
punishing yourself for it. and...
I can't...
bear the thought of that.
So can we make a deal
right now that we're even.
and just wipe the slate clean
and no guilt and no responsibility?
If we're gonna be together.
I don't want it to be out
of a sense of obligation.
Or-or even that we should be.
because of what we've been through.
I-I... I just want to start over.
Start over.
Okay.
But. uh. does that mean
I have to divorce my wife?
Because you're still married
to a Russian stripper.
Well. "A": I've been a little busy.
and "B": I'm pretty sure she was Czech.
Hey. Michael.
What's wrong?
Whatever it is. it ain't it.
I don't understand. I thought
you said we copied the card.
No. we did.
But according to the encryption code...
Okay. how do I make this clear?
If-If Scylla was like a
pizza. all we got's a slice.
So where's the rest of the data?
I don't know.
I mean...
I mean. I don't know how
we didn't see this coming.
I mean. it-it-it makes perfect sense.
It's like the nuclear launch codes.
You don't give all that
information to just one person.
How many do you give it to?
Okay. that quote your father held onto
in The Odyssey. Scylla
is a six-headed monster
that requires a
sacrifice of six soldiers
in order to pass.
So Scylla isn't one card.
it's six.
What does that mean?
How we gonna find
five more of these things?
Michael! Michael!
I'm busy.
I don't care what she looks like.
Three tablespoons of water.
one of honey.
Nothing more.
If she knows something about
anything that's going on.
I'm going to find it.
Rise and shine. bitch!
Breakfast.
Michael?
Hey. Michael!
You all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
All this security makes you wonder
what the Company's hiding.
Only way to know for sure is
to find those five other cards.
see for ourselves.
Think we'll have enough time?
Yeah.
We'll. uh...
We'll be fine.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today